https://www.reallysimplesystems.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to primary navigation Skip to content Skip to footerPrivacy & Cookie PolicyThe Really Simple Systems Privacy & Cookie Policy DetailsReally Simple Systems Privacy PolicyReally Simple Systems Ltd, a company registered in England with the registration number 1827381, takes your privacy seriously and we act in full compliance with all current UK and EC data law and directives. By using our web site and services you are agreeing to us collecting and processing your data in the manner described below.GDPR ComplianceReally Simple Systems complies with The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Where required, before we send you emails promoting our products and services we will ask you for your consent, and for an audit trail, we will record when you gave consent and from what IP address. We are registered under the UK Data Protection Act Z951270X.Collecting and Using Personal InformationWhen you visit our web site we use cookies, data from your browser and IP address to record and personalise your visit, such as showing you the correct pricing and contact details. We also use that data to track how effective our marketing campaigns are.If you give us your contact details, including name and email address, in order to register for a webinar, sign up for a newsletter or a CRM system, or for any other purpose then we’ll hold that data in our own CRM system.If you sign up for a CRM system or otherwise give us your consent we’ll use that data to send you emails promoting our services and information about how to use the CRM system and product updates. We will do so for a reasonable time period unless you ask us not to at any time by unsubscribing.We will hold your personal information securely and safely from unauthorised access. If you would like a copy of your personal information or that information deleted, just contact us.We don’t share that information with anyone outside the company, and we certainly will not pass it to third parties for them to contact you.CookiesWe use cookies on our site to better understand our site visitors and customers. If you are a subscriber to our CRM system then the cookie can also hold some of your login information to help you log in faster. If you don’t want us to use cookies then you can block them using the privacy settings in your browser. If you disable cookies completely then you won’t be able to use our CRM.Legal requests for data accessWe will only grant access to personal information if compelled to do so by a UK court or under UK legislation. Requests from other governmental agencies will be politely declined.Payment ProcessorsIf you use a paid-for CRM system then we may pass some of your personal details to our payment processor to allow them to charge your credit/debit card, or for a direct debit. We don’t store your credit card details ourselves, they are stored by our payment processor, apart from the type of card, the last four digits and the expiry date.Subscriber AgreementIf you use our CRM system then your usage will be covered by our Subscription Agreement and if you use our Marketing Module our Sending Policy.Retrieving and Removing your Personal InformationIf you wish to see what information we hold about you, want us to correct, update or delete any information that we hold on you, please contact us.Changes to this AgreementWe may make changes to this policy as the law and circumstances change. Continued use of our site and/or services will be deemed as acceptance.July 2020
